export const data = [
    {
        question: "The software tools that allow a computer to be used for specific purposes are called:",
        option1: "firmware",
        option2: "terminals",
        option3: "hardware",
        option4: "application programs",
        ans: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "When a program becomes a part of the silicon chip it is called:",
        option1: "software",
        option2: "hardware",
        option3: "firmware",
        option4: "embedded",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "The branch of computing that attempts to make the computer exhibit imagination and insight is called:",
        option1: "artificial intelligence",
        option2: "multimedia",
        option3: "hypermedia",
        option4: "computer graphics",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Mainframe computers are capable of communicating with several users simultaneously by:",
        option1: "using a terminal",
        option2: "using a supercomputer",
        option3: "using a workstation",
        option4: "timesharing",
        ans: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "Computers that are used to control temperature and humidity in buildings are considered to be:",
        option1: "software",
        option2: "special-purpose",
        option3: "general-purpose",
        option4: "analytical engine",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Integrated circuits are housed in:",
        option1: "vacuum tubes",
        option2: "transistors",
        option3: "software",
        option4: "silicon chips",
        ans: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "'Hot spots' that respond to mouse click in a HyperCard stack are called:",
        option1: "buttons",
        option2: "fields",
        option3: "links",
        option4: "cards",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "An important point about hypertext and other forms of hypermedia is that:",
        option1: "data can be stored in a sequencial format",
        option2: "it is more prone to viruses than other media",
        option3: "data can be linked in any conceivable way",
        option4: "they can be transmitted over networks more quickly than other media",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "The computer term MIDI is a name for:",
        option1: "a military informational display system ",
        option2: "a tool for creating Many Individual Data Interfaces",
        option3: "a Macintosh tool use to search for the IDs",
        option4: "a standard interface for connecting computers and electronic musical instruments",
        ans: 4,
    },
    { 
        question: "A set of rules for the exchange of data between a terminal and a computer, or between two computers is called:",
        option1: "modems",
        option2: "protocol",
        option3: "bps",
        option4: "transmissions",
        ans: 2,
    },
]